I've still got a lot of years ahead of me
この想いを　消してしまうには
Kono omoi wo keshiteshimau niwa
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
Mada jinsei nagai desho?
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
I want to go back and finish
やり残してるコト
Yarinokoshiteru koto
The things that I've yet to finish.
やり直してみたいから
Yarinaoshite mitai kara
I was supposed to be chasing after my ongoing dream,
夢のつづき　追いかけていたはずなのに
Yume no tsuzuki oikaketeita hazu nanoni
Yet I faltered over others while walking this thin, winding path.
曲がりくねった　細い道　人につまずく
Magarikunetta hosoi michi hito ni tsumazuku
It's not that I want to return to those days.
あの頃みたいにって　戻りたい訳じゃないの
Ano koro mitainitte modoritai wake ja nai no
I'm searching for the sky I lost.
無くしてきた空を　探してる
Nakushitekita sora wo sagashiteru
Don't make that sad face, as if you've fallen victim.
わかってくれますように
Wakatte kuremasu youni
As if you want people to pity you.
犠牲になったような　悲しい顔はやめてよ
Gisei ni natta youna kanashii kao wa yameteyo
Tears aren't the end of your sins.
罪の最後は涙じゃないよ
Tsumi no saigo wa namida ja nai yo
You have to bear them painfully, forever.
ずっと苦しく背負ってくんだ
Zutto kurushiku seottekunda
Who are you waiting for in the maze of emotions,
出口見えない感情迷路に
Deguchi mienai kanjoumeiro ni
Where you can't even see the exit?
誰を待ってるの？
Dare wo matteruno?
I want to blurt it out more justly,
白いノートに綴ったように
Shiroi nooto ni tsuzutta youni
Just like how I wrote it in my white notebook.
もっと素直に吐き出したいよ
Motto sunao ni hakidashitai yo
What do you want to run from?
何から　逃れたいんだ
Nani kara nogaretainda
That thing called "reality"?
…現実ってやつ？
Genjitsu tte yatsu?
I just want to scream out,
叶えるために　生きてるんだって
Kanaeru tame ni ikiterundatte
"I'm only living to fulfill my wish." Can you hear me?
叫びたくなるよ　聞こえていますか？
Sakebitaku naru yo kikoeteimasuka?
I can't take the safe way out of everything.
無難になんて　やってられないから
Bunan ni nante yatterarenaikara
I don't even have a place to return to.
…帰る場所も無いの
Kaeru basho mo nai no
I'm always thankful for everyone's kindness,
優しさには　いつも感謝してる
Yasashisa ni wa itsumo kansha shiteru
That's why I want to become stronger. (I'm on the way)
だから強くなりたい(I'm on the the
(I'm on the way)
Dakara tsuyoku naritai (I'm on the way)
This is reminding me of the old days.
懐かしくなる
Natsukashiku naru
This pain is all right with me.
こんな痛みも歓迎じゃん
Konna itami mo kangei jan
Ed and Al infiltrated the former Research Laboratory 5,
seeking the secret of the philosopher's stones.
賢者の石の秘密を求めて
元第五研究所に侵入したエドとアルは
There, they encountered people who had their souls affixed to suits of armor.
鎧に魂を定着させた者たちと遭遇
Due to what Number 66 said during their battle, Al started to question whether he was a faux soul, created by Ed.
戦いの中
ナンバー６６の言葉により
アルは自分が
エドによって作られた
紛いものの魂ではないかという疑念を抱くのだった
Looks like you're able to get up now.
起き上がれるようになりましたね
What happened to Research Laboratory 5?
第五研究所は
About that...
それが
It was blown up by someone and has been completely destroyed...
何者かに爆破され　跡形もなく
Dammit!!! It's all gone?!
くそ　全部パァかよ
はっああ　痛てぇ
O-Oww...
D-Dammit...
くっ　くっそ
I was so close to the "truth", too!
もう少しで真実とやらが掴めそうだったのに
I can't be sitting in a hospital like this!
入院なんかしてる場合じゃねぇ
Mr. Fullmetal Alchemist!
鋼の錬金術師殿
We apologize for the rudeness in advance!
先に無礼を　詫びておきます
Huh?
Doing whatever you wanted...
勝手なことをして
If things had gone badly, you would have died!
下手したら命を落とすところだったのよ
Instead of trying to do everything by yourselves, rely on the people around you!
なんでも自分たちだけでやろうとしないで
周りを頼りなさい
It wouldn't hurt to trust your elders, don't you think?
もっと　大人を信用してくれてもいいじゃない
That is all!
以上
Please forgive our rude language and violence toward a higher-ranking officer, sir!
階級にあるまじき暴言と暴力　お許しください
N-No...
あっいや　悪かったです
My fault.
Punishment... for the slap, sir?
ビンタの　お咎めは
No, I wouldn't dream of it!
そんなもん　ないない
Why do you guys try to be so considerate around me?
なんでそんなに気ぃ遣うんだよ
Because being a State Alchemist is equivalent to being a Major in the army.
国家錬金術師は　軍の少佐に相当しますから
I didn't get my state qualification for something like that.
オレはそんなもんのために
国家資格を取ったわけじゃないし
You guys don't need to be so polite to me, either.
敬語だって　使う必要ないよ
Oh, really?
あら　そう
Wow, all those times have been a waste, haven't they?
いや　気ぃ遣って損したかな
What a quick change!
順応早っ
Oh... now that I think about it, where's Al?
あっ　そういえばアルは
I scolded him with a fist earlier.
アルフォンス君は　さっきオレが拳骨かまして説教した
Ow...
痛て
I forgot about the other person who's going give me a scolding.
もう一回　盛大に怒鳴られるイベントが残ってた
Hello? You've reached the Rockbells,
specializing in prosthetics and orthotics.
はい　義肢装具のロックベルでございます
Ed?
エド
It's rare for you to call.
あんたから掛けてくるなんて珍しいじゃない
U-Umm...
あ　あのさぁ
This is extremely difficult for me to say, but...
言いにくいんだけど
Do you mind taking a trip to Central for a little maintenance?
セントラルまで出張整備してくれないかな
Trip?
出張
Well...
いや　右腕がな
It's my right arm.
My fingers move, but I can't lift my arm at all.
指は動くけど
腕がまったく上がらないんだ
So it was no good, after all.
やっぱりダメだったか
Huh?
No, no, it's nothing.
いやいや　こっちの話
Did you do something before your arm stopped moving?
動かなくなる前になんかした
I-I was in an all-out brawl.
派手にケンカした
AGAIN?! Quit using my automail for things like that!
またあんたは　私の機械鎧をなんてことに使うのよ
H... Hello?
も　もしもし
Miss Winry?
ウィンリィさん
I guess there's no choice.
しょうがないわね
Where in Central?
セントラルのどこ
Hey, you're kind of nice tod-
なんかお前　今日は優しあっ
I mean... Nothing...
いや　なんでもねぇ
Okay. Gotcha.
うん　うん
Sorry for the trouble.
悪ぃな　頼むよ
Yeah.
うん　じゃあな
Thanks.
A love call to your girlfriend?
彼女に電話
Who's my girlfriend?!
誰が彼女か
How boring.
なんだ　つまらないな
When I was your age, I had...
オレが君くらいの年ごろには
Huh?
あれ
What are you doing over there?
何やってるんだ　そんなとこで
Hey, Al!
おい　アル
Brother...
兄さん
Want to head to our room?
部屋に行かないか
Hm?
No, it's nothing.
ううん　なんでもないよ
I'll meet you there.
先行ってて
Okay.
Bye!
バイバイ
...maybe you're an armor doll that your "brother" created?
兄貴とやらに作られた鎧人形じゃねぇのか
Oww, my rear...
うぅ　お尻痛い
I don't see how Ed and Al can ride these things all the time.
エドたちよくこんなの乗ってられるわね
He said there'd be someone waiting for me at the
west gate, and I'd be able to spot him right away, but...
西口で目印が立ってるから
すぐ分かるって言ってたけど
Oh.
アームストロング少佐
Major Armstrong!
Ah, Miss Winry!
おお ウィンリィ殿
Where are those stupid Elric brothers?
エルリックのバカ兄弟は
To tell you the truth...
実は
Ed's in the hospital?!
エドが　入院
Th-That was fast.
は　早かったな
You're planning on charging me a rush fee, aren't you?
さては　特急料金取るつもりだな
But... you were injured this badly when your automail broke, because I...
だって　私がきちんと整備しなかったから
機械鎧が壊れて
...I didn't equip it properly, right?
こんな大ケガしたんでしょ
べ　別にウィンリィのせいじゃねぇよ
I-It's not your fault or anything!
I'm the one who used it recklessly,
and the maintenance was perfect, as always.
元はといえば　オレがムチャな使い方したからだし
整備はいつもどおり完璧だった あははっ
He didn't notice the missing screw?
ネジの締め忘れに　気がついてない
And there's also the fact I didn't have to get hurt more because my arm broke!
それに腕壊れたから
余計なケガしなくって済んだともいえるしさ
So don't worry about it! Yeah? Yeah?
気にすんなよ
なっ　なっ
So it all works out?
って結果オーライ
あはっ　んじゃ　早速出張整備の話だけど
Okay, so about this maintenance trip!
On second thought, I'll be charging a rush fee!
やっぱり特急料金付きね
Huh?
You didn't drink your milk.
牛乳残してる
I... don't like milk.
牛乳　嫌い
And that's why you're so short!
そんなこと言ってるから
あんたはいつまでたっても豆なのよ
Shut up!
うっせぇ　嫌いなもんは嫌いなんだよ
I can't help that I don't like it!
You're being picky, Edward Elric!
わがままだぞ　エドワード·エルリック
All the kids drink it.
子供はみんな　飲んでるわよ
You won't get any girls if you can't drink milk.
牛乳飲めなきゃモテないぞ
Al?
アル
Al's been acting strange lately.
アルのヤツ　このごろ変なんだ
What do you mean by strange?
変って
Seems to me something's on his mind.
なんか悩んでるみたいなんだ
...maybe you're an armor doll that your "brother" created?
おめぇ　兄貴とやらにつくられた鎧人形じゃねぇのか
Just accept it. It'll make you feel better.
認めちまえよ　楽になるぜ
There! Maintenance complete!
よし　整備完了
Awesome!
やった
It's finally fixed.
ああ　やっと治ったぜ　サンキューな
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
どういたしまして
Yo, Ed!
よう エド
So I heard you're kind of occupied after bringing a woman into your room.
病室に女連れ込んで色ぼけてるって
She's just my automail mechanic!
ただの機械鎧整備士だって
Wow... so you sweet-talked your mechanic, huh...
整備士を誑し込んだか
When I say one thing, you come up with another!
ああ言えば こう言う
I'm Maes Hughes.
マース·ヒューズだ　よろしくな
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Winry Rockbell.
ウィンリィ·ロックベルです
Won't you get in trouble for ditching work?
いいのか　仕事サボって
No need to worry!
心配無用
I left Sheska with overtime work.
シェスカに残業置いてきた
What are you, a demon?
あんた　鬼か
Oh yeah, you guys are almost free from your escorts.
そういえばお前たち
間もなく護衛対象から外されそうだぜ
Really?!
ほんとかよ
Escorts?
護衛って
Hey, you...
ちょっとあんた　どんだけ危ない目に遭ってるのよ
Just what kind of dangerous situations are you getting yourself into?!
Well, look. How should I put it...
いや　まあ　その　なんだ
I-It's not a big deal.
た　大したことじゃねぇよ
That's right.
そうね
You two never tell me anything, anyway.
どうせあんたら兄弟は聞いたって言わないもんね
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
じゃあまた明日ね
I'm going to go look for a place to stay for the night.
私は今日の宿を探しに行くわ
What?!
何っ　だったらうちに泊まっていけよ
Then stay at my place!
But...
でも
Don't worry about it!
気にすんなって
My wife and daughter will be delighted.
女房も娘も喜ぶしよ
No, but...
いや　あの
All right, it's settled!
よし　そうしよう
Huh?! Wait!
えっ　あの　ちょっと
Come on, let's go!
ほらほら行くぞ
うぅ ちょっとぉ
Hang on!!!
Happy birthday Elicia!
エリシアちゃん おめでと
U-Umm, Mr. Hughes? What exactly is...
あっ　あの　ヒューズさん　これって
Why, thank you for asking.
よくぞ聞いてくれました
Today is Elicia's birthday, so to speak!
今日はエリシアの誕生日なのだ
So to speak!
なのだ
So how old are you now, Elicia?
いくつになったの　エリシアちゃん
Tw-
ふた
Three!
みっちゅ
Sh...
かっ かっ
She's...
So cute!
かわいい
I've been with them ever since we were little, so they're kind of like my brothers.
あいつらとは　小さい時からいつも一緒で
兄弟みたいなものですよ
You must always be worried about them with the way they are, aren't you?
あんなだから　心配ばっかだろ
You bet!
ほんとですよ
They came home after such a long time,
and Ed's arm was in pieces.
たまに帰って来たと思ったら
腕オシャカにしてるし
And when they called me up, Ed's severely injured...
呼び出されてみれば　エドは大ケガしてるし
...and Al's being troubled by something...
アルはなんか悩んでるし
But they'll never tell me what happened.
だけど　何があったかなんて絶対言わないんですよ
Even when they left Resembool...
リゼンブールを出るときも
They probably didn't feel the need to discuss it.
相談する必要がなかったんだろ
They probably thought that you'd understand, even if they didn't tell you.
ウィンリィちゃんなら
言わなくても分かってくれると思ったんだよ
But... there are some things in life that will only be understood through words.
でも　口で言わなきゃ伝わらないこともあります
I guess that's just the way things are.
しょうがねぇよな
Guys always convey things with actions, not words,
男ってのは言葉より行動で示す生き物だから
so if it's something tough, they don't want others to have to put up with it.
苦しいことは
なるべくなら自分以外の人に背負わせたくない
They don't want to worry people, either.
心配も掛けたくない
So they don't say it.
だから言わない
But even then, if those brothers happen to whine...
それでも　あの兄弟が弱音を吐いたら
...you comfort them and set them straight.
そんときは　きっちり受け止めてやる
I think that's perfect.
それでいいんじゃないか
Elicia, let's play!
エリシアちゃん　遊ぼ
I'm getting off!
下りる
Here you go.
はいどうぞ
Hey! Elicia's going to be playing with me!
なんだよ　エリシアちゃんは僕と遊ぶんだよ
What? I'm  going to be playing with her!
ええ 僕とだよ なんだよ…
Your daughter sure is popular.
娘さんモテモテですね
No!
She's mine!
Hey, you brats!
おい　小僧ども
Do something to my daughter and see what happens!
うちの娘に手ぇ出したら　ただじゃおかねぇぞ
You don't need to convey things with actions that  much!
行動で示しすぎです
Are you sure?
本当にいいの
You can stay here for as long as you're in Central, you know.
こっちにいる間ずっと泊まってもらってもいいのよ
No, that would be too much trouble...
そこまで甘えるわけには
She's gotten so attached to you.
すっかり懐いちゃって
From this perspective, they almost look like sisters.
こうして見ると　姉妹みたいだな
Winry!
おねえちゃん
Have a nice day!
いってらっしゃい　早く帰って来てね
Come home soon, okay?
Looks like it's decided.
今日の宿も決まりね
It's like I have a little sister now!
妹ができたみたいでうれしい
So you came again, bastard.
今日も出やがったな　こんにゃろう
You've got a living body...
兄さんは　生身の体があるんだから
...so you have to drink it.
飲まなきゃダメだよ
I can't help that I don't like it!
嫌いなもんは嫌いなの
I'm actually growing, despite how I look.
こう見えてもちゃんと伸びてんだぞ
But everyone just calls me puny...
んなのにちっこいちっこいって
You've got it easy, Al.
アルはいいよなぁ
Since you're so big already.
体がでかくってさ
I didn't become like this because I wanted to!
僕は好きでこんな体になったんじゃない
M-My bad...
わ　悪かったよ
You're right.
そうだよな　こうなったのもオレのせいだもんな
It's my fault we became like this, after all.
That's why I want to get your body ba-
だから元の体に戻してやりたい
Is there really a guarantee
I'll be able to return to my old body?!
本当に元の体に戻れるって保証はあるの
I'll make it come true.
オレが戻してやる
Believe in me.
信じろよ
Believe?!
信じろって
What am I supposed to believe with this empty body?!
この空っぽの体で何を信じろっていうんだ
Memories are just information if you really think about it!
記憶だって　突き詰めればただの情報でしかない
It should be possible to create them artificially!
人工的に構築することも可能なはずだ
What are yo-
お前　何言って
Brother, you once told me there was something you couldn't say to me because you were too afraid, right?
兄さん
前に僕に怖くて言えないことがあるって言ったよね
Could it be you were trying to say...
それは　もしかして
...that I'm just a fake... an artificial soul and a set of memories you created?!
僕は　魂も記憶も
本当は全部でっちあげた偽物だってことじゃないのかい
Winry, you and Granny are both trying to deceive me, aren't you?
ウィンリィやばっちゃんも
僕をだまそうとしてるんだろう
Am I right, Brother?!
どうなんだよ　兄さん
Are those the thoughts you've been holding in?
ずっと　それをため込んでたのか
Is that all you've got to say?
言いたいことは　それで全部か
I see.
そっか
Ed...
エド
Ed!
Al, you...
アルの
IDIOT!!!
バカ
W-What was that for?!
いっ　いきなりなんだよ
Winry?!
ウィンリィ
You moron!
アルのバカちん
You don't even know how Ed feels!
エドの気持ちも知らないで
What Ed was afraid to ask you...
エドが怖くて言えなかったことってのはね
あんたが自分を恨んでるんじゃないかってことよ
...is whether you hate him or not!
It's all... my fault...
全部　オレのせいだ
He can't even eat, sleep, or feel pain anymore...
あいつ
食べることも眠ることも
痛みを感じることもできなくなっちまった
He... He hates me for sure...
絶対　オレを恨んでる
Al wouldn't.
アルはお前を恨むような子じゃないよ
Why don't you just ask him?
聞いてみれば分かるだろ
I... I'm scared...
こ　怖いんだ
I'm too scared to ask...
怖くて聞けないんだ
And... And yet...
それを　それなのに　あんたは
You...
Just who the heck would be prepared to
give up his life just to create a fake brother?
自分の命を捨てる覚悟で　偽者の弟をつくるバカが
どこの世界にいるってのよ
Don't you two only have each other?
あんたたち　たった二人の兄弟じゃない
Go after him!
追っかけなさい
Y... Yeah.
MOVE!
駆け足
Yes, ma'am!
はい
Brot-
兄…
Now that I think about it, I've gotten a bit rusty because we haven't sparred in a while.
そういえば
しばらく組み手やってないから　体なまってきたな
Huh?
Wha? Wa-
えっ　ちょっ
W-Wait a second, Brother!
ちょっ待った　兄さん
Hold on!
待った
Your wounds are going to open back up!
傷口が開いちゃうよ
I win!
勝った
For the first time in my life, I beat you!
初めてお前に勝ったぞ
ずるいよ兄さん
That wasn't fair, Brother.
Sh-Shut up!
う　うるせぇや　勝ちは勝ちだ
A win's a win!
We've always fought a lot, haven't we.
小さいころから　いっぱいケンカしたよな
Yeah.
Now that I think about it, we fought for the dumbest reasons, didn't we?
今思えばくっだらねぇことでケンカしてたな
Like who gets to sleep in the top bunk.
２段ベッドの上か下か　とかね
Yep.
ああ
We fought over snacks, too, didn't we?
おやつのことでもケンカしたっけ
We also fought over toys.
おもちゃの取り合いもやったな
I won.
僕が勝った
Even when we played by Raine River...
レイン川で遊んだ時も
You pushed me in, didn't you?
オレ川に突き落とされたっけ
We fought all the time during our training, too, remember?
修行中もケンカしてたよね
That was a draw since Master nearly beat us both to death for being "annoying".
「やっかましい」って師匠に半殺しにされたから
ドローだろ　あれは
We also fought over who would marry Winry.
ウィンリィをお嫁さんにするのは
どっちってケンカもした
げっ　そんなの覚えてねぇぞ
I don't remember that!
I won. But she said no.
僕が勝った　でもフラれた
I-I see...
あっ　ああそう
Are you going to tell me all that was a lie?
全部ウソだっていうのかよ
I'm sorry...
ごめん
We want to return to our bodies, no matter what it takes.
どんなことしても元の体に戻りたいって
Are you trying to say those feelings are artificial, too?
あの気持ちも作り物だっていうのか
They're not.
作り物じゃない
That's right.
そうだ
We decided to return to our bodies together, for sure.
絶対に二人で元に戻るって決めたんだ
We're going to be moving forward!
どんどん前へ進むぞ
If we move forward, we'll get stronger, both physically and mentally.
前へ進んで　ケンカも心ももっと強くなるぞ
What about milk?
牛乳は
I'll drink it!
飲む
...as much as possible.
んんなるべく
Let's get stronger.
もっともっと強くなろう
Yeah.
Mr. Hughes.
ヒューズさん
There are things that can only be conveyed through words. Don't you agree?
やっぱり口で言わなきゃ伝わらないこともありますよね
You're right.
そうだな
Brother...
兄者　師父
Master...
Where... did everyone...
みんなどこへ
Hi.
やあ
You're not an Ishbalan, are you?
イシュヴァールの民ではないな
Ah, pardon me.
ああ　失敬
I haven't introduced myself yet.
挨拶が遅れまして
この地区の殲滅を担当する
I'm a State Alchemist who is going to be in charge of destroying this area.
国家錬金術師です
Oh, he's awake.
わっ 起きた
Where am I?
ここは
You're in the slums on the outskirts of East City.
イーストシティの外れにあるスラムじゃよ
Sir... you are...
ご老人　あなたは
I'm Ishbalan, just like yourself.
お前さんと同じイシュヴァールの民じゃ
Don't worry, I won't sell you out or anything.
安心せい　身内を売ったりはせん
Are there other Ishbalan survivors in this place?
ここにはほかにも　イシュヴァール人の生き残りが
There sure are.
ああ　おるとも
Even a soot-covered place like this feels like a city if you live here.
こんなすす臭い所でも住めば都というか
In other words, "All of this world is within the bosom of our God, Ishvala."
「世の中すべて　我らが神イシュヴァラの懐なり」じゃよ
そうですか
I... see...
Don't push yourself!
ムリすんなよ
You were floating around in the sewers, covered in wounds.
傷だらけで下水道を流れてたんだぜ
Hey...
なあ　オレの右腕は付いているか
Is my right arm still attached?
Yeah, it is.
ああ　ちゃんと付いてるぜ
These tattoos are amazing.
すっげぇなぁ　この入れ墨
Yeah.
ああ　家族にもらった　大切な絆だ
It's a precious bond I received from my family...
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
Do you remember it from that day?
ねえ　君は覚えていますか
Nee kimi wa oboeteimasuka
We made a promise and a vow while the early summer wind circled us.
約束　契り　初夏の風が包む
Yakusoku chigiri shoka no kaze ga tsutsumu
And we clung close together.
二人　寄り添った
Futari yorisotta
Your forced smile
無理な笑顔の裏
Muri na egao no ura
Holds elongated shadows.
伸びた影をかくまう
Nobita kage wo kakumau
I pretend not to notice and continue on.
だから　気づかぬふり　再生を選ぶ
Dakara kizukanu furi saisei wo erabu
All the while waiting for you to deliver some news at the table.
テーブルの上の　震えない知らせ　待ち続けて
Teeburu no ue no furuenai shirase machitsuzukete
Empty nights, mornings that will never arrive,
空白の夜も　来るはずのない朝も
Kuuhaku no yoru mo kuru hazu no nai asa mo
I could see them from a mile away.
全部わかってたんだ
Zenbu wakattetanda
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
I'm sure you'll remember it one day.
ねえ　 いつか思い出すでしょう
Nee itsuka omoidasu deshou
While holding the promise we couldn't keep,
果たせなかった　約束を抱いて
Hatasenakatta yakusoku wo idaite
We take our first steps down our own paths.
二人　歩き出す
Futari arukidasu
日本語字幕仕上げ：FAYFAY
親友は やがて戦友となり
Your best friend eventually becomes your comrade-in-arms, and finally, an everyday fixture in your life.
そこにいることが当たり前の存在となった
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
Even if the future you discussed had turned into a shade of lead, your best friend hadn't changed and was always there.
語り合った未来が今
鉛色にくすんでいるとしても
親友は変わらずそこにいた
次回　鋼の錬金術師　FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
第十話　それぞれの行く先
Episode 10, Separate Destinations.
当たり前の存在
A fixture in one's life. Something like that cannot be replaced.
それは　掛けがえのないもの